shopwhiz.net 2018-02-23

# Privacy Policy - shop-whiz.com

Here at Shop-Whiz.com, we take your privacy seriously. We understand the importance of protecting our users’ personal information. By visiting or using this website, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways listed below. Please read the information listed below to learn more about our Privacy Policy.

  1. WHY Shop-Whiz.com COLLECTS USER INFORMATION:

We gather various types of personal information from our users for a variety of reasons. We may use this personal information to personalize your experience, improve our services, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to analyze how our users utilize the website, and for other reasons set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may share certain types of personal information with third parties (please see below).

  2. INFORMATION COLLECTED AUTOMATICALLY: 
    * Whenever you interact with our website, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser data including your IP address, “cookie” information, and the page you accessed. “Cookies” are identifiers we transfer to your computer or mobile device that allow us to recognize your browser or mobile device and tell us how and when pages on our website are visited. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or mobile device to prevent or limit your computer or device’s acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our website’s features. Our advertising partners, which may include advertisers, advertising agencies, and ad networks, may also transmit cookies to your computer or device, when you view or interact with one of their ads that appear on our website. If you click on a link to a third party website, such a third party may also transmit cookies to you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.
    * When we collect usage information (such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our website), we only use this data in aggregate form, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. For example, this aggregate data tells us how often users interact with the website, so that we can make the website as appealing to as many users as possible. We may also provide this aggregate information to our partners; our partners may use such information to understand how often and in what ways people use our website, so that they can also provide you with an optimal experience. We never disclose aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally.
  3. WILL Shop-Whiz.com SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IT RECEIVES?

We neither rent nor sell your personal information in a personally identifiable form to anyone. We share your personal information in personally identifiable form with third parties as described below.

  1. Advertisers: We allow advertisers, advertising agencies, ad networks, and/or merchant partners (collectively, “Advertisers”) to collect information about our users (including demographic information) for the purpose of providing you with advertisements specifically tailored to your interests. You agree that we may provide any of the information we have collected from you in non-personally identifiable form to an Advertiser, in order for that Advertiser to select the appropriate audience for their advertisements and/or offers.
  2. Affiliated Businesses and Third Party Websites: In certain situations, businesses or third party websites we are affiliated with may sell items or provide services to you through our website (either alone or jointly with us). You can recognize when an affiliated business is associated with such a transaction or service, and we will share your personal information with that affiliated business only to the extent that it is related to such transaction or service. For example, if you purchase a voucher through the service, we may share certain information about you with the applicable merchant, in order to allow that merchant to redeem that voucher. Another such service may include the ability for you to automatically transmit Third Party Account Information to your website profile, or to automatically transmit information in your website profile to your third party account. We have no control over the policies and practices of third party websites or businesses with regards to privacy or anything else; if you choose to take part in any transaction or service relating to an affiliated website or business, please review all such business’ or websites’ policies.
  3. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will update the Effective Date of this Privacy Policy. You are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the Website after such changes have been first posted.

QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send us a detailed message to [info@shop-whiz.com](mailto:info@shop-whize.com)  We will make every effort to answer any questions that may arise, or resolve any of your concerns.

Effective Date: 01/01/2015
